&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：还记得构造函数吗
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: You remember the constructor
属性在我们的图表中，对吗？
property in our diagram, right?
从车间指出来的那个。原型回到车间。
The one that was pointing from the workshop.prototype back to workshop.
为什么在线十个我可以说是Deep JS.structor？
Why is it online ten that I can say deepJS.constructor?
Deep JS上没有构造函数属性。
There is no constructor property on deepJS.
但原因完全相同，当我要求
But for the exact same reason, when I asked for
Deep JS上的构造函数属性，它在该对象上找不到它。
a constructor property on deepJS, it doesn't find it on that object.
但是接下来它会去哪里呢？
But where does it go next?
它从Deep JS一直到Workshop.Prototype。
It goes from deepJS all the way up to workshop.prototype.
Workshop.Prototype上有构造函数属性吗？
And does workshop.prototype have a constructor property on it?
它指向什么？
And what does it point at?
它指向车间。
It points at workshop.
所以这就是Deep JS.structor与工作坊是一回事的原因。
So that's why deepJS.constructor is the same thing as workshop.
现在，这似乎意味着Deep JS是由车间建造的，不是吗？
Now, that seems to imply that deepJS was constructed by workshop, doesn't it?
但是我们知道新的构造函数是真正创建它的那个。
But we know that the new constructor is the one that actually created it.
而车间的物品几乎与此无关。
And the workshop object almost had nothing to do with it.
只是碰巧这些属性已经到位了，
It just happens to be that these properties are in place,
这些关系已经到位
these relationships are in place,
试图告诉这个故事，阶级制度已经发生了。
to try to tell this narrative that a class system has occurred.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：现在第12行，深度JS_PROTO_，对不起。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now line 12, deepJS.__proto__, oops sorry.
这里按错了按钮。
Hit the wrong button here.
深度JS_PROTO_，
deepJS.__ proto__,
这真的是一件很长的事情，我不想再说一遍了。
that's a really long thing to say, and I don't wanna say that ever again.
所以让我们给它取个更好的名字。
So let's come up with a better name for that.
事实证明，您可以使用下划线，和
It turns out that you can take underscore underscore, and
您可以将其设为双下划线。
you can make it double underscore.
或者你甚至可以缩短它，
Or and then you can even shorten that,
JavaScript中的酷孩子喜欢将这个属性称为Dunderproto，好吗？
the cool kids in JavaScript like to refer to this property as dunderproto, okay?
所以第12行写着Deep JS.dunderproto，并且
So line 12 says deepJS.dunderproto, and
看它指的是什么，它指的是Workshop.Prototype。
look at what it's pointing at, it's pointing at workshop.prototype.
换句话说，Deep JS似乎在它上面有一个属性，
In other words, deepJS seems like it has a property on it,
指向它所链接的东西。
that points to the thing that it's linked to.
除了Deep JS没有一个名为Dunder proto的属性。
Except deepJS doesn't have a property on it called dunder proto.
那么，当Deep JS试图访问Dunder Proto时，您认为会发生什么？
So what do you think happens when deepJS tries to access a dunder proto?
下一步去哪里？
Where does it go next?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：它从深JS到哪里？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It goes from deepJS up to where?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：up to workshop.prototype。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Up to workshop.prototype.
不是车间，而是工作间。原型。
Not workshop but workshop.prototype.
它上升到那个物体。
It goes up to that object.
它会问你有没有Dunder Proto？
And it asks do you have a dunder proto?
答案是，不。
And the answer is, no.
那么工作车间在哪里原型链接了吗？
So where was workshop.prototype linked?
它被链接到对象原型。
It was linked to object.prototype.
因此，如果您愿意，我们将向零线环境升级一级。
So we would go one up level to the line zero environment if you will.
我们会去找对象。原型，然后
We'd go up to the object.prototype, and
猜猜那里有个Dunder Proto
guess what there is a dunder proto on there.
猜猜还有什么，它甚至不是一个属性，它是一个getter函数。
And guess what else, it's not even a property, it's a getter function.
Prototype有一个名为Dunder proto的getter函数。
Object.prototype has a getter function called dunder proto.
现在您在第12行访问它，就好像它是一个属性一样。
Now you're accessing it on line 12 as if it's a property.
而是一个getter函数，所以它将调用它，就像它是一个函数一样。
But a getter function so it's going to invoke it as if it's was a function.
当它在object.prototype上调用该函数时，
When it invokes that function on object.prototype,
在内部，这个关键字是什么？
internally what will it's this keyword be?
呼叫地点是什么？
What's the call site?
&gt；&gt；学生：DeepJS。
&gt;&gt; Student: DeepJS.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：呼叫地点是Deep JS，对。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The call site is deepJS, right.
这就像一个函数调用，尽管没有括号。
This is like a function call even though there's no parenthesis.
所以即使在这种情况下，仍然是一致地应用相同的解除绑定规则。
So it's still that same disbinding rule consistently applied even in this case.
它在对象上调用getter函数。
It invokes that getter function on the object.prototype in
您的实例的这个上下文，它到达它并且
this context of your instance, which reaches into it and
给你这个隐藏的内部链接叫做原型链。
gives you this hidden internal linkage called the prototype chain.